Hello, everyone.
Hello.
I'm Sazuka Kanda.
I'm Mariy Morimoto.
Today we are here...
Ta-da!
I wonder if you can tell by looking at this.
Can you see it? This way
We are here in Kumamoto.
Kunasasu 2024 will be held in September.
I'm here in Kumamoto to spread the charm of Kumasasu and to talk to you all this week.
I've been talking to everyone this week
as much time as I have.
Yes, we do.
That's quite a lot, isn't it?
Quite a lot, yes.
Normally, I...
I take about five hours.
As much time as we can spare.
I'd like to go out and see if I can get Moster
I'd like to go on an outing
with a lot of people.
I'll be there.
Thank you very much for watching.
First of all, I saw the video of the two of you in Fukuoka, and I was looking for you on the phone.
So that's where you're going to be.
Yes, that's right.
So...
So I called the first one.
Go there.
Go ahead.
Look around.
That's strong.
When I come here.
The shopping district...
A little bit more.
They have an idol group
I'm Sako Tomita, of Goldfish House Hill 46.
My name is Tomita Sako.
I apologize for the sudden contact.
I'm in Kumamoto right now.
I'm working on a poster.
I'm going to Miyazaki in February.
I'm going to hold a live concert in Miyazaki in February.
I would like to put up the posters
As part of the Kumamoto campaign
I'll be making the rounds.
If you would be interested
I'd like to put up the posters at this store.
Is that all right with you?
Yes, of course.
Thank you very much.
May I head over there now?
Yes, in about five minutes.
Okay. Thank you very much.
Excuse me.
I checked with the owner.
He said it's okay for you to come to the store.
I don't know yet if I have to go.
Yes, you're right.
But I'm glad.
Directly to the owner
Yes, you should go over there for a bit.
Say hello.
Let me assure you that I will be happy to greet you.
Yes, I'll go.
Thank you very much.
We're now on Arcade Upper Street.
There are so many great stores.
There are so many great, really great stores.
I've been trying to visit all kinds of stores.
That "ice" sign is so stylish!
It's true!
Looks like a sweet shop.
Looks nice.
It looks good.
A sweet shop.
It says it's a sales shop.
Shall we go there?
Let's go.
Wow!
Wow, that's nice.
Excuse me.
We are an event group called Hinatazaka 46.
We're asking if we can put up promotional posters.
We are going to perform in Miyazaki Prefecture in September.
Miyazaki Prefecture in September.
That's right.
I'd like to put up some promotional posters.
If you don't mind.
That's totally fine.
Thank you very much.
I'm from here and I'm pretty early.
Really?
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much. It's very nice.
It's true.
I feel at home.
May I also display my work?
This is the first one.
Thank you very much.
thank you
Thank you so much.
I was really, really nervous.
I was super nervous.
It's a beautiful restaurant.
It's the best small restaurant I've ever been to.
It's been a long time since I've been to a small restaurant.
It's been a long time!
I wonder how long it's been since I've been in a small restaurant
Ah!
Mr. Homma
I love you so much!
What?
Now?
I'm sorry to keep you waiting.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
I'm still not waking up.
The images will be shown.
I'm bored here
Praise the video re 1 minute live
I heard you're out of touch this time.
Is that so?
If you have another event, let's go next time.
Let's go next time.
I have a lot of images.
Mr. Tire is here?
I don't know. Mr. Tire is here.
What's it like?
Yes, sir.
Not here.
Nowhere.
Oh, wow.
You went to try it out.
I was just trying it out.
Okay, let's go down the street.
Let's go.
Thank you for watching.
Can you come in?
Yeah, this way.
I'm just trying to figure out where to go.
Thank you very much.
I'd be happy to put it up if you'd like.
Oh, he's filming something.
He made me take it.
Why don't you come and join us?
I don't know.
TikTok?
I want to go join TikTok.
I want to meet someone from the sun.
I'd like to meet someone from the sun.
Well, sure.
I don't know...
I don't know... I'm probably filming...
I'd like to meet someone who's...
That's right.
Why don't you take a picture of me?
Swing this around a bit.
Hello.
Hello, hello.
There are people this way, too.
Oh, yeah.
Wow.
That's nice.
It's nice.
Wait.
I've been here before.
Yes, you have.
I've been there.
What? Let's definitely go.
Let's go.
Yes, ma'am.
Hello.
I'm Masako Iwasaki and this is Fotish.
Thank you very much.
We are going to have a live concert in Miyazaki in September.
May I buy the PL poster?
Thank you very much.
It's such a nice entrance.
It's a very nice department.
It's a great place to be.
How do you like it?
It's very flashy.
Very funny.
Yes, sir.
And the posters... I've seen them.
Thank you very much.
It's very nice.
By the way, I'm going to put up the posters until about this evening.
Do you have any recommendations for stores where we can put up the posters?
Do you have any stores that you can recommend?
Yes, I do.
If you don't mind, it's just around the corner.
Yes.
There's a store owned by a classmate of mine.
Oh, really?
What's it called?
A Korean restaurant called Takan Mari.
Really?
A picture of the restaurant?
Yes, that's right.
There's an interesting restaurant.
Yes.
I told him I'd like him to put up a poster in the store.
I'll take him there once.
Yes, sir.
Thank you very much.
Then, I'll let them take you to
Korean restaurant, Tadakan Mari.
Takanmari.
Excuse me.
Hello.
We're going to have a live concert in Minasaki in September.
For that, we want to spread our name in Kyushu.
We would like to put up posters in various stores.
We'd love to have them.
May I?
Thank you very much.
This is the fourth store. Thank you very much.
Continue.
Wow.
The feeling is coming.
Thank you very much.
Are you feeling set?
I don't think so.
You got a handle on it?
It's a pretty good store.
I'll ask around.
Oh, wow! Thank you very much.
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
I'm feeling a little overwhelmed.
The Hyugaizaka 4T singles.
I'm just letting you know that there's a poster station in Kyushu
I'm just letting you know that we have a poster station.
I thought I'd introduce it to you.
I hope it's okay if you go there after 5:00.
Please do.
It's just around the corner.
Thank you.
Tee Wing Tee
Teabag tee.
Thank you for all your hard work
Thank you
Delicious chicken wings!
The manager of the cafe you just visited
Mari Honda's store.
The manager of the cafe introduced us to Mari Honda's shop and asked us to talk to the store next door.
The people at that store are also contacting other stores!
That's great!
I think it would be good as a contact.
I would like to go to Ibaraki Chie-san's now.
I'm really grateful that I've been introduced to about 5 stores
I've been referred to about five shops by phone.
I didn't expect that
Mr. Nanaseki.
I was thinking...
Mr. Nanaseki...
Where were you the other day?
Oh, here?
Oh, here.
Right here.
Excuse me, hello.
Hello. - Hello.
Excuse me.
Oh, my God, my God, my God.
I'm sorry, sir, I just got off the phone with you.
Yes, yes, yes, I heard.
You're allowed to take pictures, aren't you?
Yes, thank you.
I'll bring it to a conspicuous place.
Oh, really? - Yes, really.
Thank you very much.
Are you in Miyazaki?
In Miyazaki.
We're hoping to draw 50,000 people in two days.
That's our goal.
We really want to make this show a success.
To the people of Kyushu.
I want to let everyone in Kyushu know a lot of your knowledge
I would like to share your knowledge with everyone in Kyushu.
Here it is.
It's here.
CAPTURED
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
I don't know
I don't know.
Good afternoon.
Excuse me.
Good afternoon. - Good afternoon.
Yes, ma'am.
Oh, there's a phone call for you.
I heard you.
I'm Suzuka Tomita, from Hyugaizaka 46.
What 46?
Hyugaizaka 46.
Where's Hyuuga-zaka?
Uh, where?
Tokyo
Tokyo base.
Tokyo?
Next.
May I put up a poster?
Thank you very much.
Do you have any recommendations?
Well, I specialize in...
Gold leaf and chicken.
Oh, my God!
I want some!
I want to be gilded!
I want to eat it.
I'm so glad you could talk to me like this.
I'm so happy!
I'm so excited.
I'm so happy you're here.
Come here!
Excuse me.
Good afternoon and thank you for coming.
May I put up my poster again?
Thank you very much.
Excuse me.
Oh, wow!
I'm in.
Glad you're here.
You pick the vegetables here.
Boil them right there
Yeah, boil them.
Grill, boil, boil.
Wow!
Looks delicious.
It's like a showcase.
What's this, what's this?
I know!
Showcase.
This way, this way
Bijoux Max
We put up Mr. Vegemaki!
Towards the outside
Yes, that's right.
This is amazing.
The 700th one
Wow!
Mr. Vegemaki introduced me to you.
Mr. Sports Mar Yellow
Oh!
Hello!
Hello.
Do you know Hinatazaka46?
Of course I know it.
Oh, I see.
Two people are coming, so I'll have to do some research.
Oh, how can I help you?
I'm glad.
I'll do my best.
I'll be seeing a lot more live performances at the Kyukyuu Kyokai.
Please come!
Please.
Thank you very much.
Excuse me.
Good afternoon
thank you for all your hard work
With the help of all of you who helped us
Eight more.
Eight more
I'm so happy
Really happy
It's been a long time since I've been here.
I don't know what to do
I don't know.
But it's a beautiful country, so I'm going to go there... and Marie...
I see...
There might be more.
Hang in there.
Good luck.
Marie went to negotiate.
I hope she makes it.
I hope she's okay.
Yay!
Congratulations!
I'm so happy for you.
The cucumbers.
They're so cute.
I wish I could buy you some souvenirs.
So many stores!
Here we are.
They're here.
May I keep this here for a moment?
Thank you very much.
Oh, my God!
Thank you!
Thank you very much!
I didn't know the manager was here.
Oh, it's the manager?
Hello!
Thank you very much!
May I?
Oh, my God!
You won?
Thank you so much!
I'm still buying them on CD.
Oh, my God!
Candy for my ears.
Can I ask you two something?
Oh, no.
Oh, no!
I found these little acrylics.
Oh, oh, yummy!
By the way, I found a little acrylic with Niv's face and a little acrylic with Niv's face.
Oh, Nibbly face!
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
Thank you.
Oh, oh, oh,
Oh, my hand is broken.
Your hand is broken.
Oh, oh, oh, oh,
Oh, my God!
Thank you. Thank you.
We'll be glad to have your company.
We'll be waiting for you.
Let's have some fun.
I'm glad you're here today.
Have a safe trip home.
Thank you very much.
We'll be waiting for you.
I'll be waiting for you again
Oh, my God!
Today is kind of fateful.
Fateful, oh!
Thank you very much.
Well, what should we do? And...
Well, I'm going to eat.
If there's a place to eat...
I'd love to eat.
What should we do?
Takamoto.
Wanna go for a bite?
Takamoto-san.
Takamoto-san, Ayaka-san
Hello, Ayaka-san
I'm Mr. Takamoto.
Wow, smells great!
Wow!
I'm so excited!
Let's go!
Thank you very much.
It looks really good.
You've taken time out of your busy schedule to help us!
Thank you very much.
The board shop is great!
And a lot of Yves too!
What is the name of this store?
Takamoto-san?
Takamotoya.
Thank you very much.
Where is Takamotoya?
Inada.
By the way, you know the six names, right?
Yes, I know.
There are rules. I know them well.
That's right.
You went to Takamotoya.
For the first time.
This is your first visit to Takamotoya.
In this prefecture
Miyazaki Prefecture
Miyazaki Prefecture.
That's right.
Thank you very much.
Right at the entrance.
This way, please.
This way please.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for your help.
Various.
Various
Now a grocer
There's a grocer's place
Yes, I see.
I found a grocery store.
I've been looking forward to it the most
Indeed.
And the fun.
Yay!
It's time to talk about something really long!
It's really very nice.
Thank you very much.
Good afternoon. - Good afternoon.
Hello. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
thank you
Yes, indeed, just in time for dinner tonight.
Thank you for your time.
Oh, my goodness!
Hello!
Do you know what Taco 46 is on this day?
Thank you!
Thank you very much!
If you can make it, we would love to do a show in purple, so enjoy it in September!
Please try to go!
Are you friends?
You like the inside of Okinawa?
A friend! Are you a friend!
Hello!
Today was the 15th one!
Emiliano is also good, isn't he?
Emiliano's is there! Clothing store!
Clothing store!
If that's the one, let's do it!
Really?
Really? Thank you very much!
Thank you very much!
Come on, follow me!
Thank you!
Thank you very much!
You're so fast! You're fast!
Wait a minute!
Okay?
Are you okay to film?
I'm okay to film!
Hello!
We had a live concert in Miyazaki in September, and we have to promote it!
I came to Kumamoto from Tokyo, and it's a very warm city, and today I'm putting up posters in various places,
It's ok! I'm fine!
How are you doing? I'm so happy! Thank you very much!
Thank you very much!
I hope you like it!
You like it!
I like it!
It's over here!
Are we going?
Oh, I can go!
beauty beauty
We have an announcement at the exit!
Yes!
Thank you!
Thank you very much!
Thank you very much.
Cheers.
There it is. It's so low.
Oolong tea. Oolong tea, umacha.
It stings.
Oolong tea stings.
Wow, there's smoke.
Upper bone stabbing. The pure white one is called "Vertical Bone Sashimi".
The one with a little extra fat on it is called nijuubone-sashi, and it's only available now. The meat around the belly.
Wow, nice. Hello.
Delicious.
Amazing.
Excuse me.
Impressive, impressive.
Delicious.
Double bone marrow.
Double-bone sashimi.
Yes.
Yes, sir.
I'm sorry.
Yes, yes, yes.
Sweet.
Yes, it is sweet, isn't it?
Today, we have 15 posters.
The first one was not so bad.
Yes, I honestly thought I could put up as many as 5 posters today, but
But the connection between everyone in the latter half of the day was
Amazing!
Only at Tsunemoto can you do that.
Yes, it really is!
Two Moto
I'm impressed by the connection.
There's definitely a place I want to go tomorrow.
Yes, there is. Wow.
Super cute!
Shichijo Melon Dome
Roadside station
I will definitely go there and put up a poster!
Thank you for the food!
Thank you for the food, it was delicious!
Thank you very much
Thank you very much!
I'm so happy
Wow, wow, wow, wow!
Thank you so much for saying thank you in a very
Thank you very much.
It was really delicious
It was really delicious!
I'm super happy.
It was good.
Thank you very much.
Today is my second day in Kumamoto, and it's about 9:30 in the morning.
I'm going to appear on TV Kumamoto's "Etaro Natarade-san" in the morning.
Thank you very much.
And today's special guest is Suzuka Tomita from Heisaka 46.
They are Suzuka Tomita and Mari Morimoto from Heisaka 46.
Please give them my best regards.
Smoothie and Mari were chosen.
I'm so surprised.
Of course! Our 11th new single, You're Curly Till, is out now!
We'll be at the festival in September.
I'd be happy to accept your poster if you don't mind.
Thank you very much.
We've arrived at Sakura-cho Kumamoto.
This is really where the Kumamoto Building is located.
Yes, there's a Kumamoto Building.
Let's go.
I'm here to see you, Kumamoto.
Shhhh.
I'm off then.
Do you feel like you're spending a little bit of money?
Oh! Yeah!
A lot of momentum.
A little momentum on day two.
Thank you for asking.
Yay!
Good afternoon.
thank you very much
Good work
Yes, ma'am.
Excuse me.
We are going to have a venue in Miyazaki prefecture in July.
If you don't mind, I'd like to put up this big PR pasta here.
By all means.
Thank you very much.
Oh, my God.
Cute. Cute.
I'm drawing.
Cute, cute, cute. I draw spiders, too.
I'm drawing a spider, too.
Thank you very much.
I look forward to working with you all while I'm still in my role.
We've got a human resources operation going on right now.
I heard something about a 3-year-old baby.
I wonder if that's where he's coming from.
I'm looking forward to working with you.
I'm trying to decide where to go next.
Okay.
Brown sugar doughnuts.
I heard they're famous.
I'll check out the main store here.
Sure.
Hello? Hello? Excuse me? Do you have a minute?
Thank you very much. I am a member of an idol group called Hyugaizaka46,
We are currently negotiating with Kumamoto Prefecture to put up PR posters for the festival,
I have seen a lot of pictures of the stores there, and I thought they were really nice with a variety of products,
I was wondering if you would be interested in putting up a PR poster for Kumamoto Prefecture.
Thank you very much. I am on my way there now.
Yay! I'm so happy.
Yay!
That's great! The phone negotiations were a success!
I'm so happy.
Thank you.
Hello.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much. I'm really curious.
Oh, really!
If we make it now, will we end up making it?
Cancel all of them, 250,000 to 300,000 people.
Wow!
I can't imagine that number anymore.
Too true.
That's amazing.
I look forward to working with you.
Thank you very much.
Yes, this is what you see behind us in the future.
Ta-da!
It's a melon.
We are here at the Shichijo Melon Dome.
Yes, this is a roadside station, right?
Yes, the melon has just been released.
A huge circle of melons!
There are three big melons!
Yes, melons!
Okay, let's have a drop of melon.
One drop of melon
One drop of melon.
Please say something.
Thank you very much.
We have permission to be here today.
We would be happy if you could put the monster here, in this store, and at the roadside station.
Oh, by all means.
Thank you very much.
Wow, really, there are already a lot of melons for sale!
What time do you sell out of melons?
At what time do you sell out of melons?
Around 9 in the morning.
Around 9:00 a.m. every time. What happens around the end of the day?
Yes, that's great, because you can buy melons all over the place.
That's great!
Thank you very much for putting up two sheets!
I'm going to appear on the Last M Kumamoto radio show after this.
Yes, but before that...
But before that, I'm going to show you a slide show.
Slide, slide, slide... This time, I'm not a shaved ice shop.
This time, it's not a shaved ice shop.
I don't know what it's called, Frappe Frappe.
It's called Frappe Frappe.
Yes, they have some great shaved ice there.
They have all kinds of shaved ice.
Yes, I was attracted by the menu.
I'd like to stop by.
This is Frappe Frappe.
The blue one?
The blue and white one.
The blue-and-white one. That's what I'm talking about.
Wait, what?
Excuse me. Excuse me.
Soy sauce cream cheese with Kumamoto soy sauce.
Thank you. Bon appétit.
Bon appétit.
Here it is! Congratulations!
This is a small portion of chocolate mint!
Wow, absolutely delicious!
Delicious!
Fresh.
Fresh!
Shall we go?
Oh, please, have some.
Choco mint.
Bon appétit.
It looks so delicious!
The mint is wilkier than I expected. It's so delicious.
Easy to eat. Delicious.
It's easy to eat, it's good. -Bon appétit!
I want you to try it.
Eat it, eat it, eat it.
Bon appétit!
Oh, my God.
Yum!
It's out! Here it comes! It's huge!
Thank you for the food! The shaved ice was delicious!
We hope you will put this poster up as well!
We will put it under the shaved ice menu!
Thank you very much!
May I?
I'll see you soon!
Thank you very much!
Thank you for the food!
Thank you so much!
So I checked FM Kumamoto Sun Meat!
Last but not least, this is the Kumamoto campaign.
We really want to make this the culmination of the last two days.
Seen, one drop radio
Weak right now!
Se-no, One Drop Radio
Please go!
Good evening everyone! We are
We are Inadasaka46
I'm Suzuka Tomita.
I'm Mari Horimoto.
Pleased to meet you.
Please take care of us!
Please take care of me!
Wow, I'm so happy!
Thank you so much!
First time!
Saturday and Sunday, September 7th and 8th
at Hyuga Sun Marine Stadium Miyazaki
Hyuga Fest 2024 will be held at Hyuga Sun Marine Stadium Miyazaki!
Thank you!
Thank you very much!
I met so many people who live in Kumamoto
I met so many people who live in Kumamoto and they are really warm people.
I hope that Hyugaizaka46 will reach more people like them.
I want to work even harder.
That's right.
I wonder what each and every one of us is doing.
I thought it would be a good time to make the Hyuga Festival a success.
I hope it will be a time that will lead to the success of Hyuga Festival.
I hope you all bring a lot of blood to Hyuga Fest 2024!
I'm so happy!
Do you want to do that last one?
Let's do it!
Let's do it again!
Let's do it one more time.
Let's do it again.
Love Kumamoto!
It was fun.
Thank you very much.
That was Sazuka Tomita and Mariy Morimoto from Minatatsukku46.
Bye bye.
Thank you for watching.